{
    "subject": "Hank_Gannon",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Nora_Hanen",
    "human_readable": "Hank Gannon is married to Nora Hanen.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.931686282157898,
            "question": "To whom is Hank Gannon married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9218579530715942,
            "question": "Is Hank Gannon married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9186097383499146,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Hank Gannon and Nora Hanen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9142069816589355,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Hank Gannon and Nora Hanen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8756785988807678,
            "question": "Name the person married to Nora Hanen."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8615599870681763,
            "question": "Who is married to Nora Hanen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.844855546951294,
            "question": "Who is Hank Gannon's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6306960582733154,
            "question": "What is the name of Nora Hanen's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5655673742294312,
            "question": "Who are Hank Gannon's relatives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5521580576896667,
            "question": "What is the name of Hank Gannon's partner?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hank Gannon is married to Nora Hanen.",
            "html": "yago_14194_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Hank Gannon's relatives?",
            "html": "yago_14194_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Nora Hanen's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_14194_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Hank Gannon's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_14194_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14194_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14194_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14194_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14194_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14194_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14194_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14194_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14194_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14194_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14194_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Hank Gannon is married to Nora Hanen\":\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because the documents indicate that Nora Hanen was previously married to Hank Gannon (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_14194/re-ranker-msmarco/81.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_14194/re-ranker-msmarco/14.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information that confirms Hank Gannon was married to Nora Hanen. In the document `23.txt`, it states, \"Nora Hanen went on to get her law degree at Midwestern College where she met her first husband Hank Gannon.\" And in `68.txt`, it mentions, \"For many years, Hank never knew that, while in school, Nora had had an affair with his younger brother, R.J. After Nora gave birth to a daughter, Rachel, her marriage to Hank became strained as constraints on their time and money intensified. When Rachel was five, Hank and Nora divorced.\" However, it also states earlier in the same document, \"Nora Hanen arrived in Llanview in 1992 where she would meet, fall in love, move in with and become engaged to Bo Buchanan,\" which refers to a future relationship. The documents support that Hank Gannon was married to Nora Hanen at some point before they divorced and before Nora moved in with Bo Buchanan. Therefore, the triple is correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "multiple sources state Nora and Hank divorced.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}